Philip Cowan

1667 W Hazelwood St | Phoenix, AZ | 262-353-1343 philipjcowan1@gmail.com | Portfolio Page | LinkedIn

Summary

Full stack developer, interested in using the skills that I've developed and new ones that I've yet to learn to build awesome web applications. I've worked with HTML, CSS (and various frameworks), Javascript, JQuery, Node, Express, React, Mongo, MySQL, and Git.

Education

- University of Arizona
- Full Stack Developer Certificate | May 16 2020
- Completed the course with an academic average of A+

Experience

Freelance Web Developer

December 2019 – Current

Corwin Street – corstreet@gmail.com 619-508-7685

Connolly Electric - Sam Connolly - 928-300-2566

Bartender

September 2011 – March 2020

St. Francis – Phoenix, AZ – Chef Robert Bogart, Owner/Chef/GM - 602-200-8111 The Hudson – Sedona, AZ – Aleia Woolsey, General Manager – 928-274-3048 Water Street Brewery – Grafton, WI – Emily Matejov, Manager – 262-844-9315

Shift Supervisor, Barista

June 2006 - March 2011

Starbucks Coffee Company – Grafton, WI – Andrew Coffey, General Manager